Guide to the Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files, 1892-1990 FFAL.002
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
- Multiple Artist Files, I.; 259 folders
  - Johnston-Jon (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 114)
    Johnston, Ynez, 1920-; Johnstone, Ken; Johnstone, Mildred T.; Jones, Allen, 1937-; Jones, John Paul, 1924-1999; Jones, Marshall, 1842-1925; Jones, Michael Butler, 1946-; Jones, Ronald, 1952-; Jongkind, Johan Barthold, 1819-1891; Jonson, Raymond, 1891-1982; Jonynas, Vytautas Kazimieras, 1907-1997
  - Joo-Jz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 115)
    Joseph, Antonio, 1921-; Joseph, Erne; Josephson, Arthur; Joy, Adrienne, 1950-; Jungstedt, Kurt, 1894-; Jupena, Urban; Jurysta, Gar
  - Kaa-Kas (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 116)
    Includes March 1941 Kandinsky exhibition catalog: "Kandinsky," Nierendorf Gallery, New York
    Kadish, Reuben, 1913-1992; Kaehrling, Suzanne, 1902-1985; Kahn, Wolf, 1927-; Kainen, Jacob; Kalita, N. I. (Nikolaĭ Ivanovich), 1926-; Kamihira, Ben; Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944; Kane, David E.; Kane, John, 1860-1934; Kanemitsu, Matsumi; Kapeluck, Michael; Kaplan, Jerome, 1920-1997; Kaplan, Stan, 1925-; Kapustin, Razel, 1908-1968; Karifol, Bernard; Karsh, Yousef; Karstadt, Bob; Kashetsky, Joseph; Kassman, Shirley; Kasten, Barbara; Kasten, Karl Albert, 1916-2010
  - Kat-Kea (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 117)
    Katalan, Jak; Katsushika, Hokusai, 1760-1849; Katz, A. Raymond (Alexander Raymond), 1895-1974; Katz, Alex, 1927-; Katz, Ted; Kauffman, Craig, 1932-2010; Kaufman, Lois, 1926-2002; Kaupelis, Robert John, 1928-; Kavalec, Gregory; Kay, Nancy; Kayama, Matazō, 1927-2004; Kearl, Stanley Brown, 1913
  - Keb-Kem (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 118)
    Kelley, Chapman, 1932-; Kelly, Ellsworth; Kelly, Felix, 1917-1994; Kelly, Joe Wallace, 1895-; Kelly, James, 1913-; Kelly, Maria; Kelly, Marie; Kemenyffy, Steven, 1943-; Kemenyffy, Susan Hale; Kemp, Gérald van der, 1912-2001; Kemp, LaVerne
  - Ken-Kes (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 119)
    Kennedy, Doris Wainwright; Kensett, John Frederick, 1816-1872; Kent, Norman, 1903-1972; Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971; Kepenyes, Pal; Kepets, Hugh; Kerkam, Earl, 1891-1965; Kermes, Constantine; Kerns, Ed; Kerr-Lawson, James, 1862-1939; Kerslake, Kenneth A., 1930-; Kester, Lenard
  - Ket-Kim (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 120)
    Ketel, Cornelius; Keyser, Ernest Wise; Keyser, Robert; Keyser, Thomas de; Keyser, William; Keyt, George; Khazanov, Igor; Kho, Liang le; Kienbusch, William, 1914-1980; Kienholz, Edward, 1927-1994; Reddin-Kienholz, Nancy, 1943-; Kiernan, Maria Moreno; Kim, Hŭng-su, 1919-2014
  - Kin-Kiz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 121)
    King, Robert; King, William, 1925-2015; Kingman, Dong, 1911-2000; Kinnee, Sandy, 1947-; Kinsey, Douglas, 1934-; Kipniss, Robert, 1931-; Kipp, Lyman, 1929-; Kirchner, Ernst Ludwig, 1880-1938; Kirk, Samuel; Kizina, Jean P.
  - Kj-Koc (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 122)
    Kneller, Godfrey, Sir, 1646-1723; Kjaer, Kathryn; Klaubunde, Charles; Kleinhans, Idabel; Kleint, Boris; Klimt, Gustav, 1862-1918; Kline, Franz, 1910-1962; Klipper, Maya; Klots, Trafford Partridge, 1913-1976; Kluge, Constantine; Klyova, Natalia; Knaths, Karl, 1891-1971; Knaus, Ludwig, 1829-1910; Knee, Gina, 1898-1982; Knorr, Lester; Knowles, Alison, 1933-; Koch, Gerard, 1926-; Koch, John, 1909-; Koch, Martin, 1882-1940; Koch, Samuel, 1887-1963; Kocsis, James Paul, 1936-
  - Kod-Kol (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 123)
    Koffman, Nat; Kohlmeyer, Ida, 1912-1997; Kohn, Gabriel, 1910-1975; Kohn, Misch, 1916-; Kohut, Carolyn; Kokoschka, Oskar, 1886-1980; Koller, Rudolf, 1828-1905; Kollwitz, Käthe, 1867-1945; Kolstad, Willard
  - Kom-Koz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 124)
    Komodore, Bill; Konrad, Adolph; Koop, Kathy; Kop, David van de, 1937-; Koppel, Heinz, 1919-1980; Koppelman, Chaim, 1920-2009; Korczynski, Michael; Korczynski, Ron; Kossoff, Leon, 1926-; Kotani, Akiko; Kowal, Dennis; Kowalski, Libby; Kowalski, Piotr, 1927-2004; Kozloff, Joyce
  - Kp-Kri (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 125)
    Kraft, Arthur M.; Krajnc, Toni; Kramer, Peter; Krasner, Lee, 1908-1984; Kraus, Michael G.; Krause, George, 1937-; Krause, Glen, 1914-; Krause, Lawrence; Krauskopf, Bruno, 1892-1960; Kreindler, Doris Barsky, 1901-1974; Kremen, Irwin; Kreneck, Lynwood, 1936-; Krentzin, Earl, 1929-; Krieghoff, Cornelius, 1815-1872; Kriesberg, Irving, 1919-2009; Krim, Phyllis; Krims, Les
  - Krj-Kz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 126)
    Kroll, Leon, 1884-1974; Kroutel, Ron; Kruger, Barbara, 1945-; Kruger, Louise, 1924-; Krushenick, Nicholas, 1929-1999; Kruyder, Herman Justus, 1881-1935; Kubin, Alfred, 1877-1959; Kubota, Shigeko, 1937-2015; Kubotta, Arturo; Kujundzic, Zeljko; Kulicke, Robert M. (Robert Moore), 1924-2007; Kumata, Carol; Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1889-1953; Kuno, Shin, 1921-; Kuny, Linda; Kupferman, Moshe, 1926-2003; Kupfermann, Jacques; Kurtz, Fonda; Kuruna, Daniel; Kushner, Robert, 1949-; Kwong, Eva
  - Laa-Laf (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 127)
    La Farge, John, 1835-1910; La Fresnaye, Roger de, 1885-1925; Lacey, Tom; Lachman, Harry, 1886-1975; Lackey, Francis; Lacković, Ivan, 1932-2004; LaClaire, Maurice Carnes (tradition of); LaCouriere, Roger; Laessle, Albert, 1877-1954
  - Lag-Land (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 128)
    Lagar, Celso, 1891-1966; Lahotan, Robert; Laissement, Henry; Lambinet, Emile Charles, 1815-1877; La More, Chet Harmon, 1908-1980; Landau, Jacob, 1917-2001; Landeck, Armin, 1905-1984; Landfield, Ronnie, 1947-; Landseer, Edwin Henry, Sir, 1802-1873
  - Lane-Lar (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 129)
    Lane, Christopher, 1937-; Lane, Katharine Ward; Lane, Kevin; Lanfear, Marilyn; Langlois, Espérance; Langseth-Christensen, Richard; Laning, Edward, 1906-1981; La Noue, Terence; Lansner, Fay; Lansyer, Emmanuel, 1835-1893; Lapicque, Charles, 1898-1988; Lapinski, Tadeusz, 1928-; Larco, Jorge; Lareuse, Jean; Larraz, Julio; Lartigue, Jacques-Henri, 1894-1986
  - Las-Lau (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 130)
    Lasansky, Mauricio, 1914-2012; Lasansky, William, 1938-; Lasker, Joe; Lassaw, Ibram, 1913-2003; Lasser, Phyllis A.; Lathrop, Gertrude Katherine, 1896-; Laub, John, 1947-2005; Lauck, Anthony J. (Anthony Joseph), 1908-2001; Laugée, Georges François Paul; Laurencin, Marie, 1883-1956; Laurens, Henri, 1885-1954; Laurent, Robert, 1890-1970
  - Lav-Leb (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 131)
    LaVerdiere, Bruno; Lawrence, Jacob, 1917-2000; Lax, David, 1910-1990; Lazansky, Alwyn; Leader, Benjamin Williams, 1831-1923; Lear, Edward, 1812-1888; Lear, George; Learn, D. A.; Lebadang, 1922-; Lebrun, Rico, 1900-1964
  - Lec-Leh (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 132)
    Le Corbusier, 1887-1965; Lechay, James; Lee, Amy Freeman; Lee, Doris, 1905-1983; Lee, Robert J., 1921-; Lee, Russell, 1903-1986; Lee-Smith, Hughie; Lehar, Kathryn; Lehmbruck, Wilhelm, 1881-1919; Léger, Fernand, 1881-1955; Yi, Kyŏng-su, 1941- (materials labeled as Lee, Kyung Soo)
  - Lei-Lem (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 133)
    Leibowitz, Leonard; Leichman, Seymour; Leigh, William Robinson, 1866-1955; Leighton, Clare, 1898-1989; Leis, Malle, 1940-; Leisser, Martin B.; Leitch, Nancy V.; Lekberg, Barbara; Leleux, Adolphe Pierre; Lembeck, Jack; Lemonnier, Anicet Charles Gabriel, 1743-1824
  - Len-Leo (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 134)
    L'Engle, Lucy, 1889-1978; Lenbach, Franz von, 1836-1904; Lenica, Jan; Lenney, Annie, 1910-1984; Lentelli, Leo, 1879-; Leon, Dennis, 1933-; León, Noé, 1907-
  - Lep-Lev (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 135)
    Le Parc, Julio, 1928-; Le Tord, Jacques; Le Va, Barry, 1941-; Lepic, Ludovic Napoléon, vicomte, 1839-1889; Lepper, Robert; Lepère, Auguste, 1849-1918; Lerolle, Henry, 1848-1929; Leroux, Louis-Hector, 1829-1900; Leroy, Jeannette; Lesrel, Adolphe Alexandre; Leutze, Emanuel, 1816-1868; Levee, John, 1924-; Lever, Hayley, 1875-1958; Levinson, Joel D.; Levinthal, David; Levitan, Israel, 1912-1982; Levy, Janice L., 1957-; Lépicié, François Bernard, 1698-1755; Lépine, Stanislas, 1835-1892
  - Lew-Lez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 136)
    Lewis, Gilbert; Lewis, Martin, 1881-1962; Lewis, Victor; Lewis, Wyndham, 1882-1957; Lewitin, Landes; LeWitt, Sol, 1928-2007
  - Lf-Lic (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 137)
    Lhermitte, Léon Augustin, 1844-1925; Liautaud, Georges; Libby, William Charles; Liberman, Alexander, 1912-1999; Licht, Jennifer; Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923-1997
  - Lid-Lin (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 138)
    Lie, Jonas, 1880-1940; Lieberman, Ceil; Lieberman, Howard; Liebling, Jerome; Liebman, Steven; Lievens, Jan, 1607-1674; Linares, Lynn; Lindley, Denver Jr.; Lindner, Dorothy Taylor; Lindner, Richard, 1901-1978; Lindroth, Linda, 1946-; Linn, Steven
  - Lio-Liz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 139)
    Lipscher, Richard; Lipski, Donald, 1947-; Lipsky, Pat, 1941-; Lipson, Goldie; Lipzin, Janis; Lissim, Simon, 1900-1981; Lissitzky, El, 1890-1941; Little, Philip, 1857-1942; Litto, Frank; Liu, Guosong, 1932-; Lixenberg, Cyril, 1932-2015
  - Lj-Lon (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 140)
    Lobdell, Frank, 1921-; Lobe, Robert, 1945-; Lochoff, Nicholas, 1872-1948; Locke, Charles, 1899-; Lockhart, Robert; Loew, Michael, 1907-1985; Loffredo, Silvio, 1920-; Loggie, Helen A., 1895-1976; Logioio, Vechy; Logis, Niki; Loloma, Charles, 1921-1991; London, Edith, 1904-; Longman, Evelyn Beatrice, 1874-1954
  - Loo-Lov (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 141)
    Lo Savio, Francesco, 1935-1963; Londono, Armando; Loran, Erle, 1905-1999; Lorber, Stephen; Lotterman, Hal; Louis, Morris, 1912-1962; Love, Jim, 1927-2005; Love, Kenneth; López, Hilda, 1922-1996; López, Nacho, 1923-1986
  - Low-Lz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 142)
    Lowe, Emily; Lowe, Marvin; Lowery, Daniel; Lowndes, Alan, 1921-1978; Lowney, Bruce; Lozowick, Louis, 1892-1973; Luber, Mal; Luce, Molly, 1896-; Luchian, Ștefan, 1868-1916; Lucioni, Luigi, 1900-1988; Luks, George Benjamin, 1867-1933; Lunden, Einar; Lundquist, Evert, 1904-1994; Lungberg, Bertil; Lupori, Peter, Lundberg, Bill, 1942-; Lüpertz, Markus; Lurçat, Jean, 1892-1966; Lykins, Jere; Lyons, Mitch
  - Maa-Macn (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 143)
    Ma, Pai-sui; Maatsch, Thilo, 1900-; Mabe, Manabu; Mac-Gurrin, Buckley, 1896-1971; Macaulay, David; MacConnel, Kim, 1946-; MacCurdy, Hattie; Macdonald-Wright, Stanton, 1890-1973; Machado, Ricardo; Machin, Roger; Macias, Carmen; MacIver, Loren, 1909-1998; Mack, Rodger; MacKendrick, Lilian; Mackenzie, Donald; MacKenzie, Warren; Maclet, Elisée, 1881-1962; MacNeil, Hermon Atkins, 1866-1947
  - Macr-Mag (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 144)
    Macri, Giuseppe; Maddox, Notley Warren, 1943-1980; Madrazo y Garreta, Raimundo de, 1841-1920; Maes, Nicolaes, approximately 1634-1693; Magafan, Ethel, 1915 or 1916-1993; Magalhães, Aloísio; Magliocchi, Teoflio; Magno, Salvador; Magor, Isabelle; Magritte, René, 1898-1967
  - Mah-Mam (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 145)
    Mahdavi, Rafael, 1946-; Maignon, Albert; Maillol, Aristide, 1861-1944; Malet, Guy; Mallary, Robert, 1917-1997; Mallet, Christine Barney; Mallina, Erich, 1873-1954; Maloney, Martin; Maïk, Henri
  - Man (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 146)
    Includes reproductions of four paintings by Édouard Manet: "Pivoines," "Portrait de Madame Michel-Levy," "Les Quatre Pommes," and "Les Quatre Mandarines" along with provenance and exhibition information through 1928.
    Manacher, Frances; Manchand, Jean; Manet, Édouard, 1832-1883; Mangus, Kirk, 1952-2013; Manievich, Abraham A., 1881-1942; Manley, Edna; Mann, Karl, 1930-; Manrique, César, 1920-1992; Manship, Paul, 1885-1966; Mantegna, Andrea, 1431-1506; Mantel, Richard; Manuel, Niklaus, 1484?-1530; Manville, Elsie, 1922-; Manzur, David; Manzù, Giacomo, 1908-1991
  - Mao-Marin (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 147)
    Marantz, Irving, 1912-1972; Marc, Franz, 1880-1916; Marcheschi, Louis "Cork"; Marcke de Lummen, Emile van; Marcks, Gerhard; Marcus, Marcia, 1928-; Margolis, Richard; Maria; Maril, Herman; Marilhat, Prosper, 1811-1847; Marin, Hugo; Marin, John, 1870-1953; Marini, Marino, 1901-1980
  - Mario-Mars (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 148)
    Maris, Jakob; Marisol, 1930-2016; Markell, Isabella; Marlier, Rita; Marosin, Mircea; Marquet, Albert, 1875-1947; Marquez, Judith; Marr, Carl von; Mars, John, 1953-; Marsh, Reginald; Marshall, Neil, 1950-; Marsicano, Nicholas, 1908-1991; Marsula, Daniel
  - Mart-Marz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 149)
    Martin, Maria, 1796-1863; Martin, Noel; Martin, Phillip, 1927-; Martin, Vincente; Martinez, Juan; Martinez-Pedro, Luis; Martini, Joseph de; Martino, Frederico; Martins, Aldemir; Martorell, Maria; Maryan, 1927-1977; Marzollo, Claudio
  - Mas (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 150)
    Masereel, Frans, 1889-1972; Masley, Emma; Mason, Frank; Mason, Mary Townsend; Massaro, Karen; Massey, Jack; Masteller, John; Master of Ravensburg; Mastroianni, Umberto, 1910-1998
  - Mat-Maz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 151)
    Louisa Matthíasdóttir, 1917-2000; Mather, Jay, 1946-; Mathews, Berry; Mathews, Jane; Mathieu, Georges, 1921-2012; Matsubara, Naoko; Matta; Matthes, Ernst; Maurer, Alfred; Mauve, Anton; Max, Peter, 1937-; Maxwell, Paul; May, Karl; Mayhew, Fritz; Mayhew, Pat; Mayhew, Richard, 1934-; Mazev, Petar, 1927-; Mazur, Michael, 1935-2009
  - McB-McI (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 152)
    McBeth, Lucille; McCabe, Patricia; McCall, Charles; McCartan, Edward F.; McCarthy, Frank C., 1924-2002; McClanahan, Preston, 1933-; McClellan, John, 1908-1986; McCloskey, Eunice Mildred Lon Coske, 1906-; McCombs, Bruce, 1943-; McCoy, Myrna; McCracken, Grace; McCrady, John, 1911-1968; McDowell, Mark; McDuff, Frederick H.; McFadden, Constance J.; McGarrell, James, 1930-; McGowin, Ed, 1938-; McIntyre, Peter
  - McK-McQ (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 153)
    McKee, William; McKenzie, Mary Beth; McKenzie, R. Tait (Robert Tait), 1867-1938; McLaughlin, Jan; McLaughlin, John, 1898-1976; McMahon, Franklin; McManaway, David, 1927-; McMillan, Michael; McNear, Everett, 1904-1984; McNeely, Juanita; McPherson, Craig, 1948-; NcNeil, George
  - Mea-Men (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 154)
    Mead, Roderick, 1900-1971; Meadmore, Clement; Medina, Henrique; Mefferd, Boyd; Meidner, Ludwig; Meisel, Susan Pear; Meisonnier, Juste-Aurele; Melaney, Dan; Melohs, Charles; Meltzer, Arthur; Menageot, Robert; Mentzer, Mark, 1951-; Méndez, Leopoldo, 1902-1969
  - Meo-Mez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 155)
    Merkin, Richard; Merrill, Eleanor, 1935-; Merriman, Constance E.; Mérida, Carlos, 1891-1984; Méryon, Charles, 1821-1868; Meštrović, Ivan, 1883-1962; Mew, Tommy; Meyer, Fred; Meyer, James; Meyer, Johann Georg, 1813-1886; Meyerowitz, Joel; Meyerowitz, William, 1887-1981
  - Mia-Mid (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 156)
    Mianowski, Lucjan, 1933-2009; Michaels, Pauline; Michalik, Chester; Michals, Duane; Michel, Oswald; Michel-Henry, 1928-; Michelangelo Buonarroti, 1475-1564; Midani, Akram; Midani, Watfa; Middleditch, Edward; Middleton, Samuel M., 1927-2015; Mideros, Boanerges
  - Mie-Min (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 157)
    Miereveld, Michiel van, 1567-1641; Mieris, Frans van, 1635-1681; Mihaesco, Eugene, 1937-; Mihanovic, Zvonimir; Mikus, Eleanore, 1927-; Miller, Brice; Miller, David P.; Miller, Jane Else; Miller, Kenneth Hayes, 1876-1952; Miller, Nancy Tokar; Miller, Richard, 1930-2004; Miller, Wayne; Millet, Jean François, 1642-1679; Mills, Wesley; Milton, Peter, 1930-; Minewski, Alex; Minguzzi, Luciano, 1911-2004
  - Mio-Mod (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 158)
    Miori, Luciano, 1901-; Miralhet, Jean; Miró, Joan, 1893-1983; Mishaan, Rodolfo; Mitchell, Jane; Mitchell, Wallace, 1911-1977; Mittendorf, George; Mittler, William; Miyasaki, George, 1935-; Modersohn-Becker, Paula, 1876-1907; Modotti, Tina, 1896-1942
  - Moe-Mon (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 159)
    Moffett, Ross; Moholy-Nagy, László, 1895-1946; Mokady, Moshe, 1902-1975; Moldovan, Sacha; Moll, Eduardo, 1929-; Moller, Hans, 1905-2000; Molzahn, Johannes, 1892-1965; Moncalvo, Ana Maria; Monneret, Jean; Montecino, Sergio; Monteiro, I. (Isaac), 1938-; Montgomery, Kathleen; Montilla, Manuel, 1948-
  - Moo-Moro (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 160)
    Moore, Albert J.; Moore, Howard; Moral Sendin, Armando; Morales, Armando, 1927-2011; Morath, Inge; Moreau, Adrien, 1843-1906; Moreau, Gustave, 1826-1898; Morin, Michael; Morisot, Berthe, 1841-1895; Morita, Shiryu; Morningstar, Steven; Moro, Paul; Moron, Rene; Morot, Aime
  - Morr-Mos (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 161)
    Morrill, Michael; Morris, Carl, 1911-1993; Morris, George L. K., 1905-1975; Morris, Hilda, 1911-1991; Morris, Jim; Morris, John; Morris, Robert, 1931-; Morrison, George, 1919-2000; Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872; Morvan, Jean-Jacques; Moser, Barry; Moses, Betty; Moses, Ed, 1926-; Moses, Grandma, 1860-1961; Moskovitz, Shalom, Mosler, Henry, 1841-1920; Mosley, Thaddeus, 1926-; Moss, Ben Frank, 1936-; Moss, Joe
  - Mot-Mul (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 162)
    Motley, Archibald John, Jr., 1891-1981; Moty, Eleanor; Moyer, Jeffrey; Mozumdar, Ritendra, 1927-; Mrozinski, Jan; Mucchi, Gabriele, 1899-2002; Mühl, Roger, 1929-; Muizule, Malda; Mulcahy, Kathleen, 1950-; Mulick, Sue; Mullen, Barbara; Mullen, Buell; Mullen, Jo; Mulligan, Lee
  - Mum-Mz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 163)
    Munakata, Shikō, 1903-1975; Munch, Edvard, 1863-1944; Mundy, Ethel Frances, 1876-1964; Munter, Gabrielle; Murillo; Murray, Elizabeth, 1940-2007; Myers, Barry; Myers, Legh; Myers, Myer; Myford, Jim
  - Na-Nat (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 164)
    Nadelman, Elie, 1882-1946; Naftulin, Rose; Nagano, Shozo, 1928-2007; Nagler, Fred, 1891-1983; Nahas, Nabil; Nahlé, Wajih, 1932-; Nakian, Reuben, 1897-1986; Nankivell, Frank A. (Frank Arthur), 1869-1959; Napper, John, 1916-; Nash, Katherine, 1910-1982; Nast, Thomas, 1840-1902; Natali, Enrico, 1933-; Natkin, Robert, 1930-2010; Natoire, Charles Joseph, 1700-1777; Nattier, Jean-Marc, 1685-1766; Natzler, Gertrud; Natzler, Otto
  - Nau-Nel (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 165)
    Nauman, Bruce, 1941-; Navelet, J.; Nawara, Jim; Nay, E. W. (Ernst Wilhelm), 1902-1968; Nay, Mary Spencer; Neal, Harold; Neal, Irene, 1936-; Neel, Alice, 1900-1984; Neer, Aert van der, 1603 or 1604-1677; Negreiros, Maria Thereza; Negret, Edgar, 1920-2012; Nelson, Colleen; Nelson, Don; Nelson, James P.; Nelson, Leonard, 1912-1993
  - Nem-Nez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 166)
    Nesbitt, Lowell, 1933-1993; Nesch, Rolf, 1893-1975; Nestor, James; Nestor, Lula; Nettles, Bea, 1946-; Neuhaus, Max; Neuhuys, Albert, 1844-1914; Neujean, Nat, 1923-; Neuman, Shalom; Neuquelman, Lucien; Neustein, Joshua, 1940-; Neutra, Richard Joseph, 1892-1970; Neuville, Alphonse Marie de, 1835-1885; Newman, Arnold, 1918-2006; Newman, Barnett, 1905-1970; Newman, Elias, 1903-1999; Newman, Robert Loftin, 1827-1912; Ney, Lancelot, 1900-1965
  - Ni-Nog (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 167)
    Nice, Don, 1932-; Nicholas, Donna; Nicholas, Tom; Nichols, James; Nicholson, Ben, 1894-1982; Nick, George, 1927-; Nicolosi, Joseph; Nierendorf, Meta; Niese, Henry; Niewald, Wilbur, 1925-; Nikolenko, Nikolay; Nilsson, Gladys, 1940-; Nivola, Ruth, 1917-; Noël, Georges, 1924-; Noguchi, Isamu, 1904-1988
  - Noh-Nz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 168)
    Nolde, Emil, 1867-1956; Nordfeldt, Bror Julius Olsson, 1878-1955; Norryd, Mats; North, Bruce; Northcote, James, 1746-1831; Notargiacomo, Gianfranco, 1945-; Novelli, Gastone, 1925-1968; Novoa, Gustavo; Nóvoa, Leopoldo, 1919-2012; Nowalk, Isabelle; Noyes, Sandy; Núñez, Guillermo, 1930-; Nutt, Jim, 1938-
  - Oa-On (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 169)
    O'Connell, George; O'Hara, Frank, 1926-1966; O'Hara, Frederick, 1904-1980; O'Neill, Desmond; Obregón, Alejandro, 1920-1992; Ocampo, Miguel, 1922-; Ochikubo, Tetsuo; Oestreich, Nelson; Ogden, Samuel Jr.; Ohly, Nicholas D.; Okada, Kenzō, 1902-1982; Okamura, Arthur; Olbum, Carolyn; Olds, Herbert T., 1937-; Olijnyk, Michael; Olitski, Jules, 1922-2007; Olivera, Julio; Olivera, Nathan; Olmsted, Frederick Law, 1822-1903; Olmsted, Harold; Onley, Toni; Onslow-Ford, Gordon
  - Oo-Or (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 170)
    Opazo, Rodolfo, 1935-; Opitz, Georg Emanuel, 1775-1841; Orensanz, Al; Orfuss, Elsie; Orioli, Nora; Orlando, Felipe, 1911-2001; Orozco, José Clemente, 1883-1949; Ortman, George, 1926-2015; Ortúzar Cariola, Mariano, 1931-; Orzuj, Raquel
  - Os (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 171)
    O'Sickey, Joseph B.; O'Sullivan, Daniel; Osby, Larissa; Osés, Pedro, 1942-; Oster, Gerald; Östlihn, Barbro; Ostrower, Fayga, 1920-2001
  - Ot-Oz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 172)
    Otto, Waldemar, 1929-; Oudot, Roland, 1897-1981; Oudry, Jean-Baptiste, 1686-1755; Outin, Pierre; Oviedo, Ramón, 1927-; Owen, Paul; Ox, Jack, 1948-
  - Paa-Pal (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 173)
    Paalen, Wolfgang, 1907-1959; Pabst, Camille Alfred; Pace, Joel; Pacheco, Carlos, 1932-; Pacheco, María Luisa, 1918-1982; Pacoe, Tom; Padilla, Carlos; Páez Vilaró, Jorge, 1922-; Paik, Nam June, 1932-2006; Palatnik, Abraham, 1928-; Palizzi, Giuseppe, 1812-1888; Palmore, Thomas; Palué, Pierre
  - Pam-Park (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 174)
    Ariel, 1926- (Parkinson, Ariel); Papadakos, Thomas; Papashivily, George; Parcell, Malcolm Stevens, 1896-1987; Paris, Harold, 1925-1979; Parisot, Adriano; Parker, John W.; Parker, Raymond, 1922-1990; Parker, Robert Andrew; Parks, Charles Cropper, 1922-2012; Parks, Gordon, 1912-2006
  - Parr-Paz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 175)
    Parrish, Maxwell; Parsons, Betty; Pascin, Jules, 1885-1930; Pascucci, Michael; Pasinski, Irene; Passe, Willem van de, 1598-approximately 1637; Paternosto, César, 1931-; Patla, Robert; Patterson, Russell, 1893-1977; Pavia, Philip, 1915-2005; Payler, Mark; Payne, Edgar A. (Edgar Alwin), 1882-1947
  - Pb-Ped (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 176)
    Peale, Charles Willson, 1741-1827; Peale, Raphaelle, 1774-1825; Peale, Rembrandt, 1778-1860; Pearlstein, Philip, 1924-; Pearlstein, Seymour; Pearson, Henry, 1914-2006; Pearson, John, 1940-; Pearson, Marguerite Stuber, 1898-1978; Pechstein, Max, 1881-1955; Pedersen, Carl-Henning, 1913-2007; Pedersen, Douglas; Pedro, Luis Martinez
  - Pee-Pel (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 177)
    Includes Léon Germain Pelouse exhibition catalog from Ecole Nationale des Beaux-Arts, 1892.
    Pekarsky, Mel, 1934-; Pellan, Alfred, 1906-1988; Pelletreau, Elias, 1726-1810; Pelouse, Léon Germain; Peltier, Jean
  - Pem-Per (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 178)
    Peña, Umberto, 1937-; Pène du Bois, Guy, 1884-1958; Penney, James, 1910-; Pepper, Beverly; Pereira, Manuel; Pereira, Rene; Pereny, Madeline; Pérez Alcalá, Ricardo, 1939-; Perlin, Bernard, 1918-2014; Perlman, Bennard B.; Perlman, Joel, 1943-; Pernet, Jean; Perrault, Leon; Perrott, Mark
  - Pes-Pez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 179)
    Peterdi, Gabor; Peterson, Jane, 1876-1965; Petrick, Wolfgang, 1939-; Pettet, William; Pezzani, Gino, 1911-
  - Pf-Pic (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 180)
    Pfaff, Judy, 1946-; Pfahl, Charles, 1946-; Pfahl, John, 1939-; Philipp, Robert, 1895-1981; Philippoteaux, Paul, 1846-1923; Phillips, Gordon, 1927-; Phillips, James; Phillips, Jay, 1954-1987; Phillips, Matt, 1927-; Phillips, Walter J., 1884-1963; Piccillo, Joseph, 1941-; Picelj, Ivan, 1924-; Picken, George, 1898-; Pickering, H. Douglas; Pickhardt, Carl E.
  - Pid-Piz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 181)
    Piene, Otto, 1928-2014; Pignon, Édouard, 1905-1993; Pinto, Marion; Pintoricchio, approximately 1454-1513; Pion, Louis; Piper, John, 1903-1992; Pippin, Horace, 1888-1946; Pissarro, Camille, 1830-1903; Pissarro, Lucien, 1863-1944; Pitcher, Charlie; Pittman, Hobson Lafayette, 1899 or 1900-1972; Pivovar, Ron
  - Pj-Plz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 182)
    Plasstlaerd, J.; Plate, Carl; Pleissner, Ogden M.; Plochmann, Carolyn Gassan; Plotkin, Linda, 1938-; Plum, Jens; Plunkett, Edward